Hello guys.
Welcome. It's the blobs again here. I
have been very inactive and I'm really
sorry for that. But but of
course, you know, when I come on I have
I always bake some good news.
I have been very busy and have been
working on something very amazing.
Umm, we built me
and a group of my friends like
a much bigger YouTuber than me, Mr.
Night or Mars. Like if you see his name
there in the scoreboard. We have been
working on this Minecraft MP
and I think you're going to love it.
You're going to love it. You can click
on survival. You'll join our
survival world.It's quite
amazing. It's been unlooted. It's not
looted, so you'll be fine. You have
everything that you need on Diamond
Spike.Yeah, it's more than enough for
everyone. He also has.
An economic system.
You saw an economic system. If you do
slash bowl too.
The people on this server are quite rich
as you can see. Like I'm just
#7. That guy on top
is quite rich and also
do not bore you. I want to make this
assure to be video as possible.We also
have crates. I only have 4 keys,
but you can win a lot from the
crate.Indicates in the server.
Ohh you just.
You can win a lot from the crates in
this hour. You can win either, right?
Go.He loved them.
That's.
Ohh OK.
Well, it's fun 3 fun, 3 fun